pcgeducation.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - PCG | Public Consulting Group

Public Consulting Group and its affiliates (collectively referred to as “PCG”) respect the privacy of your personal information.  This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information that PCG may collect from you at its web sites (each referred to as “the Site”), what we do with that information, and with whom we may share the information.

### User agreement

* * *

Each visitor to the Site (“the User”) is encouraged to review this Privacy Policy.  By using the Site, the User is accepting the Privacy Policy.  The Privacy Policy cannot be changed by the User.  If the User does not agree to the Privacy Policy, then the User may not use the Site.

### Scope

* * *

The Privacy Policy applies to all PCG corporate web sites that are generally accessible by the public.  The Privacy Policy does not apply to password-protected web sites created by PCG for specific PCG clients, which by their nature require different uses of personal information.  The policy also does not apply to the web sites to which this web site may link.  If you choose to follow a link to another web site, please consult the privacy policy for that site. 

### Amendments

* * *

PCG may amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notice.  It is the responsibility of the User to periodically review this Privacy Policy for changes.  When amendments are made, the “revised” date at the top of the Privacy Policy will be amended accordingly.  Your continued use of the Site after an amendment constitutes your acceptance of the amendment. 

### Collection and use of User information

* * *

PCG collects two types of User information:  computer information that is collected automatically, and personal information that you enter voluntarily.

### Automatic collection of computer information

* * *

When you visit the Site, PCG does not automatically collect personal information from you or about you (such as your name or mailing address).  However, the Site does place small files called “cookies” on your computer to automatically collect and store certain types of data from the computer that you use to access the Site. This information includes but is not limited to the following:  browser and platform type (e.g., Internet Explorer browser on a PC platform); the Internet Service Provider, or “ISP” (e.g., AT&T); the Internet Protocol (IP) address unique to the computer; the number and length of visits; the pages visited; and the referral source (e.g., Google) and search terms that led to the Site page.  PCG uses this computer information to assess interest in the Site and its pages, and for other internal business purposes.  

### Collection of voluntarily provided personal information

* * *

PCG also may request and collect certain personal information from Users who wish to be contacted by PCG or to receive PCG publications such as white papers and newsletters.  This personal information may include the User’s name, email address, telephone number, and mailing address.  PCG does not request or collect other personal information such as social security numbers, driver’s license numbers, or financial account numbers.  You are under no obligation to provide any information about yourself, though certain information may be needed in order to respond to a request for information or publications.  We will not attempt to match this personal information with IP addresses and other automatically collected information, except as may be necessary to police misuse of the Site.  You may opt out of receiving communications from PCG by contacting the Site Administrator (see Section 10).     

### Disclosure of User information

* * *

User information collected through the Site is stored securely within the PCG network.  PCG does not sell or transfer your information to unaffiliated third parties, except for the purposes of the operation of the Site, to comply with applicable law (including subpoena requests), and to respond to your request.  For example, all information transmitted to or from the Site, including your computer information and User-entered personal information, may be accessible to nonaffiliated third-party vendors and contractors who provide services to PCG relating to the operation of the Site or the supply of requested information (e.g., analytics and optimization services). PCG has security agreements in place with these vendors and contractors.  User information also may be disclosed in connection with a merger or the sale of PCG assets, and User information posted by the User on a PCG blog may be accessible to anyone visiting the blog.  Aggregated or otherwise anonymous data may be used and shared for any purpose.

### Disposal of User information

* * *

Upon its determination that records containing User information are no longer are of use to PCG, PCG will dispose of such records by secure means so that any personal information is no longer readable.

### Review and changes to personal data

* * *

A User may review and update the personal information that PCG has collected regarding him or her by contacting the Site Administrator (see Section 12).

### Links to other sites

* * *

 For your convenience, the Site may contain links to other web sites of interest that are not owned, controlled, or managed by PCG, including social media sites.  These non-PCG web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and PCG is not responsible for their privacy policies.  The User is encouraged to review the privacy policy of each web site visited.

### No warranty

* * *

Maintaining the security of your personal information is of utmost concern to PCG.  PCG uses reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access.  However, no system can be absolutely secure.  Consequently, you should not transmit to the Site any health information or other information that you consider sensitive.  PCG cannot warrant the security of your personal information transmitted to the Site, and you do so at your own risk. 

### Site Administrator

* * *

The Site is administered by PCG’s webmaster. The webmaster can be contacted by email at  
[ **info@publicconsultinggroup.com**](mailto:info@publicconsultinggroup.com)  or by regular mail at:

**Revised - October 2017**

Web Site Administrator  
Public Consulting Group, Inc.  
148 State Street, 10th Floor  
Boston, MA  02119
